Thank you for watching!
Yes, please.
My heaven and earth are not eternal, that's why I shine
I dream of a future of unknown numbers
Dreaming of an unknown future
Enjoy together
The number of paths
Number of ways
Is it a mouth voice?
Yes, I'll try.
Dreaming of the future
I dream of it.
Yes, thank you.
Crying and laughing
It's high
Just for us
Yes thank you
Thank you very much
Yes please
Planetarium
The school you sneak in with
See, my heart starts to dance
Yes please
Planetarium
A school that you sneak into with a planetarium
See, my heart starts to dance with excitement
someone says you are stupid so what's wrong with that, be my baby or wait we are just my only one
I'm just my only one
someone say you are stupid so what's the big deal be my baby or wait we are just my only one
We are just my only one
The pages of your youth...
Yes, sir.
Pages of youth...
The pages of my youth
Yes. Yes.
Mmm-hmm.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, that's difficult.
Oh, it's difficult
A-ha Gaming
Oh, wait a minute
Now this shuuker
Toronto
Someone says you are stupid, so what's wrong with that, Be my baby, seriously, We are just my only one
We are just my only one
Yes, I am.
Someone says, "You are stupid," and I'm like, "Be my baby," and I'm like, "We are just my only one," and I'm like, "I'm just my only one.
It's a hamo.
I'll take a hamo.
Yes, sir.
Bamboo
Okay, I'll give it a shot.
Okay, thank you very much.
We're done.
Recording.
Bye-bye.
Yes, please.
Someone says you are stupid, so what's wrong with that?
Be my baby, seriously We are just my only one
Someone says You are stupid, so what's the big deal?
We will never fade away
I'll make a wish
I'll make a wish that this night will never fade away
We are our own heaven
Let's make a page from our youth
A dream of many colors
Spotlight till dawn
We'll always be Dreamin We've Always Been Dolly Mans
Ended
Thank you very much
Thank you for watching!
Good bye.
Yes, ma'am.
Bad wink.
Even that, Charmin.
Good bye to my wimpy self
But can I cry once in a while?
Still...
Prism with you
Become the rhythm of birth
Enjoy together
You and the prism, the rhythm of our birth
The pages of youth
Dream of colors and greens
Spotlight till dawn
We'll always be DREAMER
Thank you
Spoon Cut
Sawadie Cup
Yay.
Thank you.
Please.
With you I'm invincible so this moment
I'm invincible with you, Sfroma, in this moment
With you, I'm invincible... this moment...
Yes, sir.
This night will always be
It's just us
Crush
I'll make it happen I'll make it happen
I'll never forget
Heaven Heaven
One more time, please.
Fluttering
Will come true, will come true
I'll never lose my color
I'm sure you can make a wish
this night forever and ever
Our own heaven
Thank you very much.
Subtitles by Ishi no Kami
Crying, laughing, epiphany, the dance floor lit by stars
With you, I'm invincible, so this moment
Chuinku chuinku
Yes, please
Because I'm invincible, this moment
Chuinku.
Hmm?
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no!
A bad wink.
Even that's charming
Good bye to my wimpy self
But it's okay to cry once in a while
Someone says You are Spirty
So what's the big deal?
It doesn't matter.
Be my baby
We are just my only one
I'm not very good at winking, but even that's charming
Good bye to my wimpy self, but it's okay to cry once in a while
I can't stay forever
Let's make a wish
Let's make a wish that this night will always be
Our own
Haven
Haven.
Yes, sir.
The pages of our youth
Dreams of many colors Colorful Dreams
Spotlance till dawn
We'll always
We'll never forget
Haven
Haven.
Thank you very much.
Yes, ma'am.
This moment.
Sound
Yes, sir
Yes
Sound
Every time I get close to something, even a little scratch and fluff
Closer to adulthood
Even if the number of little scars on the journey increases
Yes
It will never fade away
I wish I could cut this year short
This night for ever and ever
Our own
Of our youth
Oh, I made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
The pages of our youth
A dream in every color
Spotlight till dawn
We'll always be
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle
Please, please, please
Because dance pro is invincible with you
Right now, right this minute
Can you make it? I'm afraid my voice is getting a little nasal.
Will you be okay with that?
I'm invincible, so this is the moment
planetarium, more sneaking into the school, you know, pounding, taking out the no-holds-barred
I'll take out the infant Remove the entrance of the many times infant
Ride on the rhythm of you and the prism
Enjoy together
The last one
Cheers!
I'll make a wish that'll never fade away
This night will always be ours
Yes, ma'am
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
I was singing.
Today.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
Crying and laughing
Every use
The stars shine
Dance floor
If it's with you
I'm invincible
In this moment
Twinkle Twinkle
What's that? Huh?
Yes!
Because with you, I'm invincible
Right now, at this moment
I'm trying to be tough, but the truth is
I'm lonely when I'm alone
Eye to eye
Step by step
Connecting step by step
The way
All through this night, all through this night
Our own
BrightlyIt's bright.
Wow.
Yes, ma'am.
You're always welcome here.
Wish me a happy new year.
♪ This night will always be ♪
Just for us
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
At this moment